- Glass of wine?
- No. SuIfites. Migraines.
(Penny:)Well, I'd offer you Halloween candy,
but that's gone.
(Penny:)- So, what's up?
- Okay, we used to go out, right?
(Penny:)Oh, my God.
That's where I know you from.
(Leonard:)I'm dealing with a situation
and it's kind of about my love life.
(Leonard:)So I know that might be weird
for us to talk about...
(Leonard:)...but in this area, as you know,
all my other friends are just so stupid.
(Penny:)All right, what's going on?
- So you're okay talking about this?
- Yes.
- Sure it's not weird?
- It's okay.
If you ever wanna talk to me
about a problem in your life with a guy...
...then l... I'd be fine with that.
(Penny:)Okay, good.
There's this one guy I used to date...
(Penny:)...who's about to be force-fed wine
and cheese if he doesn't get to the point.
(Leonard:)Okay, uh, here it is.
(Leonard:)Is it cheating
if a guy has a girIfriend?...
(Penny:)Yeah, probably.
(Sheldon:)- Come on.
- I'm sorry, go ahead.
I met this girI and she's great.
We have a lot in common.